It's time.
I can't wait.
I'm too addicted, man.
I actually wanted to start this dream like two hours ago, but I already planned it for now.
So I had to sit here and wait.
I'm gonna try not to pick Azazel this time.
Just because I've been doing so much Azazel, I feel like I should try something else now.
Now, the whole war of Babylon is very dirty.
And I don't know what's happening there.
This is a new one we got.
Kain.
Didn't really get to experiment too much with Kain.
This one is... what else do I have unlocked here?
Eden is unlocked?
Wait, Eden tokens won.
I don't know what that means.
Question marks on health, speed, and attack?
What does that even mean?
You know what?
Let's keep it simple.
Let's do Lazarus.
This is pretty much Isaac, but better.
Look at our win streak.
It's won.
We're gonna win again.
Mom?
I don't even know why that was a bit... man, it's so weird having both hands on the keyboard again.
Okay, let's see here.
Now I know how to scroll in the item descriptions.
So this is gonna be helping a lot today.
Okay, so far so good.
These guys are not scary at all.
Lazarus is pretty gold!
They explode!
Oh no!
Oh guys, it's going horribly.
I need to, you know, get back into the game here.
I keep forgetting what these enemies do.
Okay, there we go.
We got him.
Obviously, we got to go in here because this is an item.
There's enemies.
I don't know what that is.
Stem cells, shot speed, health, and oh, that's good.
That's very good.
More health is good.
Okay, moving on.
We got to kill these little fake Isaac's.
Actually, kill the flies first.
They're faster.
What are you gonna do when you get stuck in the corner?
I need to calm down, man.
I'm already too excited about this idea.
Like, I'm playing Isaac and I'm excited about getting to play Isaac right now.
How does that make any sense?
I like can't wait to play Isaac and I'm playing it right now.
Isn't that weird?
What a feeling.
Also, I just noticed the huge ass freaking sit on my face.
That's nasty stuff.
Lazarus.
Why is that?
Huh?
Kill this guy.
Nice.
By the way, this entire video you're watching right now is actually pre-recorded.
Nothing is real.
This was all recorded like months ago.
All of you are thinking this is live or super dumb.
I'm just kidding.
Am I?
You'll never know.
You will never know.
Oh my god, that's funny.
Wait a minute.
That's a cap.
I haven't had it before.
I'm gonna destroy these.
Okay, so we can actually refresh this store if need be.
I don't know if I'm gonna do it.
For some reason, mine is unlucky.
Is that just the standard for Lazarus?
I guess it is.
I didn't pick up anything that would affect that.
This is my strategy now for dealing with these guys.
It's just the run by.
Look how good that is.
I'm gonna kill this guy.
Also, we have a freaking door on the right.
That doesn't look too good for me.
Oh, that's the boss.
Right, that's how that works.
I guess we're doing the boss.
Famine, that's a new boss.
How many bosses are there?
Oh, uh-oh.
Okay, kill the little guys, man.
Oh, I got hit.
It's very bad.
Wait, maybe I shouldn't kill the small guys.
Just attack him, you know, and keep running circles around them.
Is he gonna keep spawning them though forever?
Okay, okay, okay.
Dude, I keep getting hit by these.
This is a tough boss.
Oh my god.
I'm actually dead.
This is over.
It's too hard for me.
I can't dodge all of this at the same time.
Just keep spawning them.
It's impossible.
Yeah, it's over.
Oh wait, I'm back.
Right, that's the whole point of this guy.
I keep getting hit.
I can't not get hit.
It's crazy.
Okay, when he does that, he spawns them.
So just keep running like this and without getting hit or what?
How do you even do this?
Oh man, that was close.
Oh, oh!
He's different now.
Okay, just keep dodging.
Oh, we made it!
Unbelievable!
What is this?
Ball of bandages.
Gotta lick them all.
Let's have a see.
Levels up each time it is collected.
One orbital familiar that blocks.
Wait, haven't I had something like this before?
Something with three stages?
Level two.
I don't care about level two and three yet.
I guess I'll worry about that if I find more.
I also have a pill.
One makes you small.
I don't know what that means.
There's no explanation for that.
Also, we can scroll like this now.
Nice.
Okay, good stuff.
Keep moving.
We have a familiar.
So there's a timer on this room and I don't know what that means.
I think if I do it fast enough, maybe there's like an extra reward or something.
I just lost a bunch of stats.
Wait, what?
This one blocks shots and deals contact damage.
Why did I just get a minus stat?
Oh, it's got to be related to the pill.
Maybe the pill gave me a bunch of stats and I didn't realize.
And then when I went to the new stage, that buff is gone now.
That's probably what happens.
Okay, so far so good.
I like it.
Yeah, go this way.
Oh, man, they're fast.
Wow.
Man, this is such a tight-ass room here.
I killed these small guys.
Why are they not dying?
Okay, there we go.
This guy's gonna spawn a spider.
If they're not fully sized, they're not gonna spawn anything.
The tower spawns six troll bombs in the room.
That can be bad as well, though.
I don't really want to do that.
Also, that is Q, not space.
Gotta remember that.
Oh, there is a chest down there.
I can get it.
Beautiful.
Bombs and keys.
Very nice.
I don't know what that is.
Some kind of spider potion?
Chemical peel damage up.
That sounds pretty good.
Increases the damage of tears fired from Isaac's left eye by two.
Oh, okay.
So the left eye shots are red.
I guess that's from the chemical.
And what is it with this stone here?
Maybe there's nothing to that.
I just feel like it's weird.
Okay, we got poop.
Yeah, this guy's gonna rush.
That's fine.
You can rush all he wants.
Nice.
Good stuff.
We're gonna play so carefully today.
I said that last time too, but this time I'm serious.
We're really gonna analyze every situation, not take risks.
We're What did I say?
What did I say?
Ah, these guys are nothing.
Except there's a lot of them.
So maybe a lot of nothing is something.
This could be problematic.
Kill him, kill him, kill him.
Okay, good.
Yeah, if only all rooms were these guys.
Okay, I wonder if there is something about these pots as well.
If I get enough bombs, I'm gonna try to I didn't mean to enter this.
That was a plain mistake.
I had no intention of doing this.
That was completely by accident.
Oh well.
It's not the hardest of bosses, so it should be okay.
My range even good enough to hit him.
Yeah, it's okay.
Keep running with them.
Okay, it's this way now.
A lot of flies here.
Oh, that's a lot of flies.
We're in trouble.
Maybe.
Okay, it's not it's not that bad.
It's not that bad.
Yeah, the Duke of Flies is definitely the easiest boss, I think.
What was that sound?
What just happened?
Plus one empty red health.
Chance to spawn a red heart when taking damage.
Chance increases with luck.
That sounds really good.
Except I have no luck.
I'm very unlucky.
I'm not done exploring.
Let's go back.
Still no bombs.
I wonder if there is a way to somehow trigger this bomb without using a bomb myself, because they're sort of lodged in here, right?
So it would be cool if I could somehow do that.
It would be super helpful.
Oh no, these spiders are always such a problem for me.
They're so fast.
Okay, okay, here we go.
Kill him.
Nice.
That was some good aiming there.
I'm proud of myself.
Okay, I don't see anything else suspicious in here.
I have four coins.
I don't think that's what I have.
Now there is a room in the very start that I ignored, so let's go back.
Oh, this music just gets me hyped every time I play this.
It keeps me locked in, you know?
Oh god.
Okay, okay.
Take care of the small ones first.
Looks like you got to be sort of close to them before they aggro.
Okay, nice.
Not bad.
Except I lost a blue heart.
But it's okay.
I forgot how many hearts I started with on Lazarus.
It's got to be two hearts, right?
Because I have this one, which is plus one health, and this one which is plus one empty red health.
So should I enter?
Maybe later.
Okay, these are gonna shoot.
I'm always scared of enemies that shoot projectiles.
It's like the worst.
Okay, any suspicious rocks?
Doesn't look like it.
Okay, I'm gonna hit up here.
Fuck it.
Wow, two chests!
Pills!
Oh, this is exciting.
Ah, too bad.
This one is nice.
Tears up.
The tower, what was that again?
Spawn six troll bombs.
I guess it could be good for clearing a room if there's a lot of enemies, you know?
As long as I don't get hit by the bombs myself, of course.
Okay, let's go.
It's time to move to... I mean, I have five coins.
I could check out the store.
Nah, not worth it.
I think it's worth it to open a store when you have at least ten coins.
This is my new rule that I implemented now.
There's also this place here, but that is a place where I need to give up a heart to get an item.
I'm gonna say no to that.
I'm not gonna take any of those deals today.
Okay, catacombs one.
Also, we got plus 24 on the heaven just now.
Maybe should I get a steady increase between stages?
Why is this guy white?
Okay.
Oh!
Pooping green stuff at me.
Catacombs.
Oh, two big rooms here.
These guys are tough because they have a lot of HP.
Nice.
So far, so good.
That was a waste of health.
I really shouldn't have picked it up.
It's okay.
It happens, you know.
We got batteries here.
And nothing else?
I can't believe that.
There's gotta be something going on here.
Weird.
What is that?
It's some kind of boss.
Whoa.
Let's try this.
That didn't do anything.
Oh, it spawned some spiders or something.
Oh, these guys spawned spiders.
Oh, man, that's rough.
Oh, wow.
You gotta kill the small spiders first.
Otherwise, there's too many spiders.
Okay, here we go.
Spiders gone.
Nice.
Huge.
Very good.
This is a tough one.
One of the harder rooms for sure.
I need to calm down, man.
I'm like tense all over.
It's not good for my body.
Just calm down.
It's fine.
Money!
That's a lot of money.
That means we can open this now.
Ah, 15.
What is that even?
Is that a battery?
Car battery?
It's probably gonna affect something about my energy levels or mana.
Doesn't sound too interesting.
Then again, I haven't tried it, so maybe it's not what I think.
I killed these tomatoes.
Oh, shit.
This guy's here.
I thought he was shooting him from across the canyon.
Feels good.
I'm looking for rocks that are suspicious.
I'm not seeing any.
I see a mushroom, though.
Probably doesn't mean anything.
You.
Oh my god, what was that?
Insane jump!
I almost had no time to react.
Okay, let's hit the south.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
This is like insanely difficult.
I got one.
Okay.
Man.
That is rough.
If something happens, if you distinguish that fire... Am
I hitting it?
No, I'm not hitting it.
I didn't mean to open that.
Oh, well.
I guess I want to go in here anyway.
So there's buttons.
I don't know what that does.
Knockout drops.
Chance to fire fist shots, which have much stronger knockback and confuse enemies for several seconds on impact.
Sure.
They pack a punch.
Let's have a look.
Okay, nothing more there.
Click the buttons.
Spawn some enemies.
So what is the point of clicking that button?
Why was that good?
I don't understand.
It's gotta be like a reward at the end, no?
So let me click this.
Hey, poop!
A golden variety.
Hey, okay, okay.
So maybe there's a random chance of either spawning enemies or getting something good with these buttons in the treasure room.
That is the easiest room of all time.
Getting some good money here.
Oh, this is rough.
He's got to die fast.
Okay, it's not that bad, actually.
Nice.
That's the boss.
Not yet.
I need to try and find some healing.
I'll go this way.
Ooh, hello.
Wait, the other ones don't go down.
That's not worth.
Yikes.
Oh, man.
The fists!
Like the sound effects on that.
Amazing.
Good.
This way.
Ah, I have two bombs.
I can definitely get that.
Nice.
That's huge.
Punch him.
Oh, God.
Oh, I think my thing just absorbed the attack there.
That was nice.
Coin and the stars teleport to the treasure room.
If there is a planetarium, teleport to it instead.
Hold on.
Treasure room is the one in the bottom.
So it would be a waste to use it here.
I should use it somewhere else.
Unless there is a planetarium or whatever.
I I'm just gonna save it.
Come on.
Good.
I could gamble here.
I'm gonna gamble a little bit.
Huge.
I will not go below 15 coins.
Oh, my God.
15 is my limit.
Then we're gonna blow it up at the end.
Ah, actually we're not.
We're gonna save the money.
No, we're not.
We're gonna blow it up.
I meant saving bombs.
Okay, we're at 15.
Blow it up.
What was that?
Why did the rainbow just appear?
No idea.
Maybe some kind of modifier just for the stage.
I also haven't found the secret room here.
I mean, it could be anywhere, right?
So we need to find an item that reveals the secret room.
Or I can go in here.
I mean, we do have full HP.
Yeah, let's go.
Ah, man.
Horrible idea.
RNG fucked me up there.
Okay, here.
The ice.
He got confused.
Oh, shit.
These are tough as hell to hit.
Shit!
I'm actually gonna die.
Let's kill one of them.
Oh, wow, wow, wow.
Growth hormones.
Speed and damage.
I mean, that's just good.
No reason not to take that, right?
Okay.
Kill all of this.
Maybe there's hidden stuff in there.
No hidden stuff in the poop.
Okay.
Why am I seeing health in that room?
That's a lie.
There was no health in there.
Hold on a minute.
The map is lying to me.
It's saying there's health in this room up here.
Oh, there was.
Ah, but that didn't do anything.
Shit, I must have missed that when I was there.
I'm gonna buy this now.
4.5 volts.
I didn't get to read the flavor text.
Healing damage to enemies gradually recharges active items at a rate of one charge bar per 60 damage dealt.
Active items no longer gain charges from room clears.
I knew it had something to do with that.
Pretty much useless to me.
I got no active items.
Also, I don't know how to use them.
I mean, I know how to use them, but I don't know how to use them.
You know what I mean?
We're gonna learn that today.
Today's all about active items.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, you guys tell me what that means.
It's either a butt or a pair of boobs.
There's nothing else.
There's no other explanation for that.
Oh, you're gonna poop the green stuff, huh?
I really like the the punch.
Nice, I needed bombs.
What's up, guys?
Let's crack a lacking.
I got fists for you.
Nice, I'm getting a lot of money this time around.
Very promising.
Oh, we got a nice room there.
Ah, this shit.
How did I do this?
Oh, this is almost impossible.
Oh, my god.
Oh, nice.
I actually nailed that.
Oh, hey, there we go.
Not bad, huh?
That is a... What is that?
What is that?
I don't know what that is.
Die-o?
Three-roll enemies?
Devolves all enemies in the room into other enemies of lower difficulty.
Does not affect the bosses or mini-bosses.
Okay.
Oh, d10.
It's a die.
I see.
Okay.
That sounds pretty good, actually.
Use it!
Okay, they're lower enemy... lower difficulty now.
They're smaller.
Ah!
He caught me in a corner.
Now the question is, can I use it again?
Because I have half a mana left and it cost half a mana to use, right?
I'm gonna try that in the next room and see if that is how that works.
I can't get to that card.
Okay.
Let's go here.
I'm gonna try it.
It doesn't work.
Freaking useless.
Now we have a full bar in a second here.
Now?
See, now we can do it.
Weird!
Why does it consume... Oh, wait a minute.
Now I have zero.
Maybe it does consume a full bar and I happen to get half a bar back.
That's probably what happened then.
Okay, I think I understand.
Hey!
Some money.
So here's my understanding of it.
When you use the item, it just completely empties your bar.
Your battery, you know?
But if there's multiple sections on the battery, it simply means you need more energy to refill it completely.
It means the item is more valuable to use because it costs more battery, right?
Okay.
I can go up or left.
I think I'll...
I'm gonna go up, actually.
Nice.
I feel like I'm doing more damage.
Not gonna do this one, though.
I will blow it up.
Fantastic.
Those skeletons are very dangerous.
The hit-and-run strategy is the way to go.
Nice.
Unidentified pill.
Speed down.
That's bad.
Well, there it is.
The stars.
May you find what you desire.
That one without looking.
This is the one that takes me to, I think, the treasure room.
Yeah, nice.
If there's a planetarium, teleport to it instead.
Ah, we've been to the treasure room already.
Crap.
Okay, go in here.
Nice.
Oh, that's bad.
Or, no, it's good.
This one needs to be blown up.
Wow.
Huge chest.
Hold on,
I gotta I guess I got a heart.
Fantastic.
All right.
Wait, why did I... Oh, I see.
I'm getting hearts when I take damage.
Yeah, chance to spawn a red heart when taking damage.
That means these rooms are actually especially good for me.
The ones where I lose health when I walk through them.
Getting even better with more luck.
Very nice.
Solid first run so far.
And I could go in there.
I'm gonna.
Pills.
Placebo.
Triggers the effect of the pill held without consuming it.
Variable charge based on the last pill copied.
Wait, triggers the effect of the pill held without consuming it.
Oh, this is an active item.
Right, it's not a pill.
Huh.
Confusing.
Okay, this one is just a pill.
I'll take it.
Something's wrong.
Uh-oh.
I pooped oil.
Not sure what that was.
Okay.
Maybe something happened on this stage that I don't know about right now.
It is a possibility.
Oh, God!
Fuck, that guy's huge!
Oh, my goodness!
Whoo!
How did I not lose any HP just now?
That is actually a miracle.
Very surprised by that.
Okay, I'm going down here.
Okay, so this guy's blue.
I don't know what that means.
Let's pay attention.
Wow, the fist is really good here.
Oh, he shoots.
Okay, so he shoots those.
He shoots only horizontal, though.
Oh!
Frickin' bones.
Come on, sir.
Oish, we got him.
We got him.
We got him, ladies and gentlemen.
Now, this guy, he's looking for trouble, and he found it.
Now, here, I think I can get in.
Isaac gets smaller.
Oh, that's good!
Smaller target to be hit.
One makes you small.
Oh, that's what that happened or did to me earlier.
I see.
The black one.
Bombs are key.
I don't understand that one.
Is it telling me that when I run out of keys, I can now use bombs?
As a key?
Instead?
Because bombs are key.
Right?
Maybe I can blow up doors now or something.
This guy needs to... Wow.
Nice healing.
Uh-oh.
Oh, thank God he died fast.
Kill this thing.
Kill him.
Nice.
So, these rainbow shits.
Okay.
I'm trying to look at my stats and see if anything changes.
Let's try it again.
Wait, a bozo.
What does bozo mean?
I've heard that term before, but I don't know what it means.
Kill these guys.
I hate when there's so many enemies.
Okay, good.
Oh, that's an enemy.
What a weird room.
Okay.
Tomatoes and we got spider thingies.
He's gonna spawn spiders if we don't take care of it.
Nice.
Oh my God, I'm actually killing it.
Oh, okay.
That's the boss.
We also have a lot of backup hearts in case we need it.
Down here.
Oh, no.
Oh, these are bombs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
I was a bit too close there.
So, this room is the one with the spikes.
Okay.
I can actually afford to take a bit of damage.
Get a coin.
Let's do it again.
Okay, no more now.
Now we go heal up.
Man, I'm super fast as well.
I do wonder if me getting smaller also affected my speed.
Even though that wouldn't make sense, but I don't know.
It feels like it.
Smaller legs, you know.
Can't run as fast.
Nice.
Wait, we have 11 coins.
There's nothing in the shop.
I bought everything.
There's a heart all the way to the end.
Let's grab that.
There's a good run so far.
I'm feeling good about this.
If only I could fly, huh?
Or jump.
That would be even better.
Karrion Queen.
That's a new one.
Oh, you're confused.
You're gonna poop.
Okay, you're pooping.
Oh, I have to destroy the poop, I think.
And now I can destroy you.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, no, that's a lot.
Yeah, he's immune to damage.
How on Earth are you gonna do this?
Wow, that was lucky with the HP there.
Oh, wait, maybe I have to... Oh, I have to hit him behind.
I see, I see.
He has a little vulnerable spot there.
Wow.
Thanks.
Man, this item is really paying for itself.
Wow.
Oh, no.
Get rid of the poop.
Ah!
This is a crazy boss.
Really difficult.
I'm gonna destroy some poop here.
Yeah, we did it!
Wait, does the poop count as his HP as well?
That's what it felt like.
Cat on Nine Tails.
I've had this one before.
More damage and shot speed.
That's just good all around.
Very good.
Okay.
Oh, wait, they keep it.
Never mind.
Ah!
I thought the boss spawned them.
What the hell is this?
Don't need too much candy.
That's one.
We got a hundred percent on the fucking cross thingy.
Hold on a minute.
I need to think.
I also had this item, the active item.
I don't really use it.
I should use it more.
And I think I'm gonna use this item now.
Watch.
Hey!
Spelunker hat.
See-through doors.
Nice.
Reveals the map up to two rooms away.
Reveals icons for nearby special rooms on the map.
Prevents damage from falling projectiles.
Wait, what does that mean?
Falling projectiles?
Does that mean projectiles going down on the screen?
Or does it mean projectiles that... so when you shoot a projectile, it has a range, right?
At some point, it's gonna fall down and hit the floor.
Maybe you don't take damage at the very end of that range.
You know?
Holy shit, he has a lot of HP!
Ah!
I'ma start in a corner here.
Oh, man.
Rough.
I'm gonna try and destroy this.
Nothing.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wait.
These only take damage from behind.
I have no idea.
I guess a Saze will just damages them on both sides.
Oh, the more you learn.
Okay, let's go down.
Oh, what is this demonic shit?
What's happening here?
I have a feeling, guys.
I'm an idiot because I have an item that actually reveals these things.
I shouldn't have done that.
I learned my lesson immediately.
Everything's fine.
Nice.
And these should be deactivated?
Yes?
No?
Okay.
This is where I spawned.
Wow.
I need more range.
That's what I need right now.
I can't enter there.
It's too risky.
Not with this amount of HP.
Uh-oh.
And then he dies, okay?
Okay.
Oh, crap.
Oh, wow.
Got it.
This is getting very dangerous.
What's up, dudes?
Come on.
Okay.
Any suspicious rocks for me?
No?
Okay.
I got a lot of bombs.
Nice.
Very smooth.
I need some HP, though.
This one is sus.
What?
It was differently shaded, wasn't it?
It was a little bit lighter.
Oi, oi, oi.
Wow.
Grab the heart.
Okay, so when they jump, you want to be diagonally to them.
That's the key to those guys.
Okay.
This is some kind of miniboss room, I think.
Let's not do that just yet.
Let's get punched, noob.
Oi, oi, oi.
Look at me aiming.
Ha!
That went pretty well.
Very good.
Oh, secret room!
But wait, we don't have an entrance.
Maybe it's from the downstairs area.
Yeah.
Nice.
You know, I could also use those enemies, the bomb enemies, to destroy walls.
But that's like some high-level stuff, you know.
That is some galaxy brain moves there.
So the problem is, I don't know which of these walls I can destroy.
Let me try this one.
Nice!
Thanks.
That's it?
Is that it?
Really?
That's kind of sus.
Oh, let's not forget, I have an active item.
That's on space.
Use it!
Make them smaller.
Nice.
Any rocks?
No, no rocks.
Ooh, honestly, I don't really want any of this.
Maybe this one.
I'll take that.
Nothing else was really that exciting in there.
There's another secret here!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Right here!
Nice!
He wants coins.
All right, some.
Have a lot.
More.
What if you give these guys a hundred coins?
Ooh!
Supper!
Oh, that was huge!
Plus one health, heals one red heart!
Damn!
Very nice.
Destroy this thing.
Yeah!
Give me that.
Man, blowing those things up is always worth it.
Okay, what now?
Okay, we got a mini boss room and a boss room.
Let's go to the mini boss room.
Galatini!
Oh, shit.
I would lose that fight nine times out of ten in real life.
Oh!
Whoa, that was a fast comeback there.
Very nice.
Man, that's a lot of HP.
Damn!
Okay, time for the boss.
There's a battery in here, it seems.
Except I can't get to that.
I could if I use two keys.
It's not worth it.
The gate!
Right, you did that stuff.
Oh!
How do you even see that coming?
Wow!
Okay, that's not too bad, man.
I'm killing it!
Nice!
Got it!
Wonderful.
Baby bottle?
No, Tropicamide.
What was that again?
More range, that's so huge.
Increased tier size is also good.
Oh my goodness, that's a big size tier now.
Love it.
I think we're ready to move on.
There actually, there is a room at the very top I would like to go to, because we do have extra hearts.
I'm totally min-maxing this right now.
I can lose some HP, it's all cool.
Oh, right.
Wait, what if I destroy you?
I can't.
All right, fine.
Wait a second!
How?
Blow it up?
Oh, okay, that works.
Aw, man!
Come on!
That's sad.
It is what it is.
Time to move.
And maybe grab some HP on the way out.
Yeah, there's a bit of HP there.
Thank you!
Moving on.
Lazarus, baby!
That's two.
Oh, I have an active.
Let's be ready with the active, in case she hits the... Actually, I think I can handle this one.
I don't need the active here.
Nice.
Huge.
Wait, you're shooting stuff at me.
I didn't even see you.
Feel like I need more damage.
I don't have enough.
This is like a mini boss room.
Sloth.
Wait, Sloth is about money, right?
No, no, Sloth is being lazy.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the different synths.
The magician.
What was that one?
The current room plus three range.
Ooh, actually kind of good.
Maybe we'll use that against the boss.
What do we have here?
We can buy it.
Bogo bombs!
One plus one, boom.
All bomb pickups become double bombs.
Does that mean I just get two bombs when I pick it up?
Or does it mean when I use a bomb, I place down two bombs?
I will find out, I guess.
Hmm, should I go up there?
Not yet.
I'm scared of those long hallways.
Jesus.
I think it's only the red ones that jump.
Yeah, the other ones don't.
I mean, they jump too, but they don't jump far.
Yeah, let me try this now.
No, that's definitely just one bomb, so it's two bombs you get by picking up now.
Oh, wow!
Didn't even see that guy.
Okay, okay, okay.
Get the small guy.
Nice, he's gone.
I need that health.
Oh my god.
How did I get hit?
Oh, wait, he spawns the small guys, I think.
I could be wrong.
Whoa.
Yeah, I think I'm wrong.
He doesn't spawn them.
You got him, though.
Look at the rocks.
No sus rocks.
A pencil.
Lead pencil.
Every 15 shots fire a burst of bloody tears.
Cool.
Oh, wait, this rock is... Oh, wait, that was the rock this thing was on.
Alright, okay.
What was this thing pointing up in here?
Oh, is that a key symbol?
That doesn't look like a key symbol to me.
Not worth it.
We have so many keys.
Wow.
Hey, I'm taking damage in the blood.
At least I think so.
Oh, that was a lot of... You see those tears?
That's crazy.
Yeah, don't walk in the blood.
Bro, I need to get used to that.
That's not something I'm used to at all.
Secret rooms.
Wait, what's going on here?
Load that up.
What's that?
Chaos!
That sounds like it could be bad.
Spawns one to six pickups.
All item pedestals draw from random item pools.
All item pedestals draw from random.
Isn't it already drawn from random item pools?
Oh, no, actually, I guess it's not.
Because some items only spawn in certain places, right?
Like this one only spawns by killing a boss.
So it's all like completely randomized now.
But to me, the end user, I don't feel a difference, I guess.
On Bilgle Court, when entering a room with half red heart or less, gain a little Steven familiar that fires homing tears.
30% chance when taking damage to spawn a Gemini familiar for the current room.
Chance increases with luck.
Okay.
Fetal protection.
Very good.
Magician is the ranged one.
This one is.
Plus more damage.
Oh, I like that.
What's that one?
Ancient recall.
Draw three cards.
Yeah, do that one.
Ancient recall.
The hermit.
Teleport to the shop.
Reveals the map.
That sounds pretty good as well.
Spawn six.
No, that one is horrible.
I'll use this one.
Cool.
I'm low on HP here.
Yo, wait a minute.
Could I not simply maximize this?
Watch.
One, two, three, four, five, six, wait, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
And then next time I enter a room, I go boom.
Look at that shit.
The magician range.
Yeah, give me that one, I guess.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, seven, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
Are you ready?
I'm gonna slap.
Boom!
He got
shotgunned.
Okay.
What a weird room.
How do I actually proceed?
I guess I can access here.
Yeah, okay.
As long as I'm... Yeah, okay, I should be safe here.
There we go.
Except I can't get in there.
Yes, I can.
Please give me HP now.
Imagine that explosion killed me.
I would have been uh... Obsetti spaghetti for sure, if that happened.
Whoa!
I still got hit somehow.
Ah!
The magician!
It's over!
I can't, I can't think.
Oh my goodness.
Wow.
Uh-oh.
Make them smaller.
It didn't work, because these type enemies.
Uh-oh.
It's really bad.
Wow.
I keep forgetting about that.
Wowie.
Okay.
Man, I need to calm down.
Hold on, I need to take a sip here.
Wow.
Okay.
Ah!
Shit!
Immediately into it, huh?
Okay.
Wait, I soon have a big one coming.
There it is.
Yeah.
Whoo!
Man, oh man.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen.
Fourteen.
I'm primed and charged.
Haha!
This feels so dumb.
Haha, but it's so good.
Let's wait.
Get him.
Nice, nice, nice.
Okay, it's boss time.
Uh, shit.
Should I?
Or should I do the other room first?
No.
It's time.
Oh, it's mom!
What?
I didn't think it was gonna be mom!
I gotta pay attention to what's happening!
So, she's yelling, I sick!
Yes, what is it mom?
What do you want?
Okay, okay.
I saw that one coming.
Oh, wow.
I'm dead.
Oh, man.
Man, I should have looked at whatever I needed to look at to realize that mom was coming up.
That was, that was rough.
That was a rough one.
But it was a good, uh, it was a good warm-up game.
Solid warm-up, for sure.
Now we're in it.
No more mistakes.
Look at this.
It's two of spades.
Doubles Isaac's keys.
If Isaac has no keys, gives two.
Uh, let's wait with that.
Sponsored blood donation machine.
No, I want to take this pill.
One makes you small.
Okay.
Temperance, which one was that?
Right, the blood donation thingy.
Okay, and then this one, I'm gonna keep that, I guess.
Oh, this is gonna shoot me.
Except it can't.
And I can't get there, so it's kind of a weird situation.
It's a butt.
Mega bean.
Giga fart.
Release a giant fart that poisons, petrifies, knocks back, and deals a hundred damage to all enemies.
Destroys obstacles and breaks open doors.
Whoa!
That is a massive fart indeed.
Will that poison hit me as well, though?
I hope not.
Wait, why is the map saying there's something in here?
Oh, now it's gone, okay.
I have no money, so that's useless.
We're gonna try this immediately.
Ready?
Holy shitballs!
That was a giant fart!
Holy crap!
Alright.
Very nice.
Oh, yeah, it needs a lot of battery.
Look, this one's gonna take a while to recharge.
I see how it is.
I see here.
This is evil!
Evil fire!
It's gone.
Wait, what?
Oh, I have no keys.
What a weird situation.
I always have keys.
But I guess I can get keys.
Yeah.
That's the consolation prize.
That's a stat increase based on whichever one is the lowest.
Which one is my lowest?
Speed or shot speed, I guess.
Huh?
I gained range?
That wasn't my lowest.
That was my highest.
This thing is lying to me.
So confusing.
I would love to get this pill.
Yeah, something is wrong.
I don't know what, though, but something is wrong.
This is a weirdly suspicious room.
We're not gonna go boss yet.
There's a bomb here.
Not worth it.
This could be worth it, actually.
Let's do it.
I think there may be a bomb in there.
Oh, hell yeah, totally worth.
Should I go in here, though?
Now, that room is weird.
I feel like that room sucks ass.
It's not good.
It's time for the boss.
Let's go.
There's a coin here.
Not worth it for one bomb.
The haunt, okay.
That's fine.
The giant fart is not ready, unfortunately.
So the question is, how does energy actually recharge now?
Now that I don't have this item that recharges energy when I deal damage?
Like, what is the standard setup for energy recharge, you know?
Maybe it's clearing a room.
Something similar, something like that.
Okay, he's gonna shoot things at me randomly now.
Yeah.
Stay a little ahead of him.
Up to my shots.
Beautiful.
In fact, I have an idea.
Oh-ho!
Suck on those bombs!
And don't take that.
This one is good!
Nice.
And then we take this.
Yeah, very good.
Okay, there's a timer on this one, but you know what?
I don't care.
I'm not even gonna worry.
I'm gonna go in here.
These rooms always slap.
Yeah!
Oh!
Chip and die!
I'm in trouble!
Oh no!
It's too early!
I'm not ready for this!
My goodness.
Kill the little dude.
Oh god, you fast.
Okay, it's not actually that hard to kill.
We're chilling here.
Come on.
Good.
Nice!
Dude, am I just killing this guy or what?
Look at me go!
I'm running circles around him!
Too easy!
Jesus juice!
Oh, that sounds good!
Damage and range.
Love to see that.
We got demon shit in there.
I don't think I want to do that.
I'm not into that stuff.
Here we gotta do drive-bys.
But the blue guy, he is going to shoot, I believe, bones.
Because he's blue.
I could be totally wrong about that.
Nice.
Oh no, he shoots normal stuff.
Man, these guys are actually super tough to kill.
Oh my god!
Taking so much damage here.
I can't push the TNT!
I was hoping I could push it to the bottom and then destroy it.
I thought I was being super smart here for a second and then I couldn't even do it.
Okay, you need to die.
There you go.
You want to jump over here?
Good.
This guy's poison is bad for me.
I like the Jesus juice.
That's what Lazarus needs.
It's so fitting as well, you know?
Jesus came back, so did Lazarus.
Holy shit.
You gonna jump?
Yep.
More like charge.
It feels so weird when I'm so small.
I like it though.
Wow!
Beautiful.
I feel like I have bad aim.
Oh, I started here.
Actually, go here.
Oh god.
Let's not forget we have a mega fart right now.
In case we need it.
This one I've seen before.
Replaces all chests that spawn with red.
So is that good or what?
I don't know if red chests are better.
I feel like they're not.
What about the golden chests?
Those are amazing, right?
But since it's an item, I guess it's better.
What else is the point?
Let's go in here.
A pill!
It's smaller even more!
Ha ha!
Look at us!
We're tiny!
Tiny baby Lazarus.
That is so cute.
Yeah, very good.
I have no money, so rip.
It's down here.
Tiny Lazarus can't be stopped.
The one-eyed man is back.
Scan the rocks!
Clear!
I'm taking this door.
What is that?
It's a mini red butt.
It's a kidney bean.
Love tuts.
Huh?
Oh, fart that charms nearby enemies.
That is a very low-cost item, though.
This one's better.
This one's insane.
Insane.
Wait, we already completed this stage.
Let's leave.
We're done here.
It's getting out of this shithole.
Stage four.
No, stage three.
I need to pay attention to when we're at the boss or the mom stage.
So I don't accidentally fall for the mom thing again.
Holy crap.
Ah, too close.
Too close.
Oh.
Ha ha!
Can I bait them?
Come here.
Hey!
Sick.
There's probably a million small details like that in this game you can utilize if you're really good, you know?
These fucking guys are hard as hell.
Oh, that's a fat explosion.
Oh, I got hit too, though.
Too bad.
That is a fruit.
A juicy sack.
Oh.
Okay.
Spider baby.
Following familiar that generates a trail of slowing creep spawns blue spiders each time a room is cleared.
That sounds really good.
Nice.
We got lucky there.
Let's see if we get lucky again.
We did not get lucky again.
Too bad.
Okay.
Limited amount of places we can go.
That's what I'd like to see.
I killed a red one, I guess.
Really annoying enemies.
Aha!
I guess I'm gonna blow it up.
Nice.
It's always worth.
But maybe if you deposit like a hundred gold, maybe it's worth to do that instead.
Oh my god.
Yeah, this guy needs to die first.
That's for sure.
How did I not get hit just now?
Okay.
I think this creep is really good.
Because you want to kite enemies anyway, right?
This allows you to do it even better.
Except, of course, if they're flying and they don't care.
Bomb for a key, that's worth in my current circumstance.
Oh no!
I hate these enemies.
Wait, am I so small I can't get hit?
Hold on a minute.
What's happening here?
That projectile just flew straight over me.
What the?
Wait a minute.
I'm not gonna test it, but I'm gonna try and pay attention.
Oh yeah, okay, okay, okay, got it.
Stay up here then.
So the red ones just shoot more projectiles.
See how it is?
Oh my god.
You bastard.
Come here.
Red chest?
Okay, that's pretty good.
Do like that.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Let's do.
Blow him up.
Yeah.
We gotta do it at some point, right?
Otherwise it's wasted.
Come on, spiders, help me.
Okay.
We got a little bit of money.
A blue pill.
Should we take the chance?
Wait, is one battery gonna refill my entire bar?
Because that could be huge.
Should
we gamble on the pill?
I think it's worth, because the more we know about the pills, the better pills become throughout the run, right?
Nice!
That is a massive pill!
Huge pill that just went into our stomach.
Let's not do the boss.
Not quite yet.
Uh-oh.
Holy shit.
I'm stuck.
I'm okay.
Everyone's just farting here or whatever.
Nice.
Wait, he's not even shooting at me.
He's just randomly shooting.
Let's see, one battery?
Okay, does not fill the entire bar.
I think that was three tiny bars.
So look at this rock in the center compared to the other rocks.
That's a dark-ass rock.
This one is sus.
What do you mean?
Why were there no secret?
It was differently colored!
What the hell?
Oh, shit.
All right, watch this, watch this.
Come on!
Yeah!
Insane!
Nice!
No coins from any of these.
Wow.
Very unlucky.
Time for the bomb.
I mean, time for the boss, not bomb.
But we are going to have a big-ass fart bomb ready for this boss.
I'm going to use it.
Pestilence.
All righty.
All this looks really good.
Fuck you!
Why do you shoot the bombs that explode?
Very good.
We cannot walk on the green stuff.
Freaking nailed that.
Oh, we've had this one before.
This is a cube of meat.
That was the other one where we could have a level up on it.
Block shots and deals contact.
That's good.
Okay, moving on.
Why is everyone just crying in this game?
Every character is lying on the floor just absolutely bawling.
Oh, that's not an enemy!
How come that exploded?
Oh, the guy is shooting it.
I see now.
Wait, is he still going to shoot me?
No?
Okay.
I could walk through this thing.
The problem is, it's going to consume my blue heart.
That's kind of a waste, but whatever.
Okay, that was not worth it.
I gambled and I lost.
You know what the problem is with my current setup here?
My character is so small, I literally can't see where my character is, because my familiars are bigger than me!
So I'm misjudging where my character is half the time.
Jesus!
Nice.
Thanks.
I'm gonna blow him up.
That is fantastic.
I hate these long corridors.
Like the way I'm keeping track of where my character is, is where my projectiles are.
Enjoy!
Okay.
Man, that thing that spawns hearts whenever I take damage has paid for itself so hard.
In fact, oh yeah.
Nice.
I'm not gonna pick that heart up yet.
We're optimizing.
Ouch!
Holy crap, that hurt.
Now we're picking it up.
Uh... I feel like my damage is not very good.
What is that?
Okay, we're gonna blow everything up.
Boom!
Man, that item is good!
Holy cannoli!
Like it's game changing how good that item is.
It totally saved me.
Okay, I don't want to go to boss yet.
So these are the red ones.
They jump up in the air and they do the thing.
Yeah, there it is.
Man, I deal no damage.
Okay, he's down.
Wait, something just spawned.
I think.
Or maybe it's just a door opening.
What is that?
Hyromaniac!
Oh, that's the one where I can't take damage?
Getting hit with an explosion heals you!
Yeah!
Very good.
Wait, so I'm immune to fires, is it?
And really?
Oh, cool!
Very nice.
Now we just need a lot of bombs.
In fact, a new strategy I can do is go in a corner, place a bomb, and wait for enemies to come near me.
Imagine that.
Oh, Lazarus looks kind of messed up in his head.
He's seen better days for sure.
I'm so fast that my creep cannot even keep up here.
What's up, dudes?
The only problem is I have no damage.
Oh, god.
Wait, even the projectiles have slowed in this creep?
Oh, shit.
Wait!
This heals me!
Oh, my god!
The freaking gas explosion healed me!
What's up, nerd?
Hey!
Oh, my goodness!
This is kind of broken, though.
Oh, we're gonna blow that up.
Oh, wait, I need to run from the bombs.
We're totally chilling.
Uh, I don't know if that's worth it using a bomb for.
Probably not.
That's crazy.
Pyromaniac is goaded.
Just create a whole freaking creep area here, and then lure them in.
And that is a lot of small guys.
Maybe my main source of damage is gonna be bombs, because my tears are definitely not doing it.
Okay.
So, he shoots a little diagonally.
Cool.
They all do, okay.
Oh, wait.
These one heal me, I guess.
Let me try.
Yo.
It's insane.
Heal this guy.
Nice.
Amazing.
Okay, we're going north.
More bombs is good.
We like bombs.
What's this?
Even sma- Let's do it.
We're going all in on the smallness.
Soon I can't see my character anymore.
I'm just a little pixel.
That's funny.
Uh, I don't have enough money to buy that bag, unfortunately.
I would love to.
Ooh, wait.
No, I can't get to it.
Wait, unless I blow it outside.
No.
Fuck!
Too bad.
Wait, am I sliding around on the white stuff?
No, okay, okay.
No, I'm not.
Money!
We didn't kill the boss yet, right?
No, no, no.
Boss is still alive.
Oh, wow.
Jesus.
Wait, why is this guy not taking damage?
Ah, right.
He needs to do that first.
Let's wait.
Nothing suspicious in here.
There's a door I can't open here, and a door here.
Cry more, cry more.
Cry for me.
That's it.
I love when you cry.
Give me those tears.
Now it's boss time!
Oh yeah, we even have a heart in here we can grab.
Nope, never mind.
I mean, actually, we could access that, but we need two bombs.
I don't want that.
Too much, but I can go in here, and then in here.
Shit!
Ah, but this is one bomb.
We can do it.
I'm an idiot.
I could have healed myself with that bomb.
Ah, whatever.
Yeah, boss time.
I have such trouble seeing where my character is.
I wonder if there's some way to highlight my character location.
I don't know what active cam is.
Bullet visibility.
Oh, okay.
Too bad.
Here we go.
Gertie!
Would you like a bomb?
Wonderful.
Magic scab.
More luck.
Aye, we need that.
More health!
Holy crap.
We're getting a lot of health.
That's gonna be huge.
Okay, so this is a fifth floor.
Or depth one, I guess, whatever.
This door's open.
Trinity shield.
You feel guarded.
Lock shots in the direction Isaac is firing.
Ooh, wait, really?
That sounds really good!
What the frick?
That sounds extremely good.
Uh-oh.
Oh, wait, that heals me.
Haha, I should not be afraid of that.
These guys are fast.
Ah!
What's happening?
Oh, I'm standing on the blood!
I see, I see.
What the f... I can't see where I am!
Okay, I'm here, I'm here.
Man, that's confusing when you're small.
Jesus Christ.
Wait, you know what?
I could save those.
If we're being smart about this, I'll save them until I'm...
Yeah, I'm gonna save them.
I have a plan with that, guys.
You'll see what I mean soon.
Okay, gotta find the enemies.
There they are.
Bro, what?
Where are they?
There they are.
Nice, we did it.
Okay, I gotta find healing.
Or I blow myself up, of course.
Wait, I wonder if this also blocks their shots, if I have the shield.
The laser, it counts as a shot, I guess.
Let me stand over here.
Oh!
Holy crap, okay, okay, okay.
I was hoping to time it with the hand.
Didn't happen.
Um, hmm.
Oh, wait, I've seen those before.
Once before.
These, uh, oh wait, I can just use my shield.
My shield is crazy.
Hey, give me health!
Yeah!
Come here!
Okay, it doesn't quite help when I run into them, you know?
That's not the best way to do it.
Pill, what's that?
Unidentified, should we chance it?
Yeah, let's do it.
Bombs are... bombs are key.
I mean, that's good, I guess, since we have bombs.
A lot of bombs.
This one is a question mark.
I mean, why is it a question mark?
We know what that is.
Hello?
Doesn't make any sense.
Come on, I have no damage.
It's actually a big problem.
Ah, they don't get hit from the front.
They're tough to kill.
How the hell am I supposed to kill them?
Is it taking forever?
Okay, you know what?
Enjoy.
Have some bombs.
Fuck all y'all!
Wait, there's more!
Thought I killed them all.
The hanged man?
What?
Grant's flight for the room!
Cool!
Uh, which room am I gonna use that in?
Nice.
I'm using my shield.
Uh, new item?
Best friend.
Friends till the end!
Places a decoy that draws enemies to it and explodes.
Ooh.
I mean, that's healing for me.
That's healing!
We can probably use that in a smart way.
Uh, we still have some rooms.
Down here.
Man, I need to collect more bombs.
That was weirdly easy.
No.
Oh, heal me!
Oh, yeah.
I'm glad I realized last second.
Good.
Oh, that's funny.
This enemy has, like, a different enemy on the back.
And not just a brain.
I want to find more secret rooms.
Okay, let's try this.
No, no, let's not waste it now.
I'm gonna use it somewhere else.
Maybe here.
I'm gonna use it here.
Cool.
This is a black shit.
What does that mean?
Things got really dark in here.
Let's put all the effects.
Okay.
Move on.
I'm gonna go to the south again.
We've got a couple rooms down here we can utilize.
I also have a couple blue hearts somewhere.
Oh, shit.
Wait, this doesn't block lasers at all!
Okay, so lasers are not good.
Cannot block those.
Wow.
Jesus Christ, bro.
I'm just not doing any damage to these guys.
Fucking butt faces.
Uh, let me get in there.
Okay, I'll take it.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Now, do I go inside of there?
Or not?
I'm gonna use my blue heart on that, but I think it may be worth it.
Come here.
I can't even like aim for the items on the floor because I'm so small.
I think I like my big fart more though.
I may have to go exchange that right now.
So what I do is this.
We're gonna let it explode on us, heal us.
Nice.
And then we go exchange it for the other one.
And that is located.
Oh, where did I put that?
Oh, I see.
Up here.
There we go.
Oh, no, it's not fully mannered.
Oh, I thought it would be full mana or something.
But I guess it has the mana I left it with.
Makes sense.
Yeah, there's nothing in there for me.
Uh, didn't we also have a couple hearts somewhere?
Yeah, down there.
Wait, I'm missing something.
I left some blue.
Remember, I left blue hearts somewhere.
Was that this room?
Doesn't feel like it.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Fantastic.
And now we go.
Not that way.
Wait, no, no, it is the right way.
Then this way now.
Wait a minute, there's an X here.
Look at that.
X marks the spot.
Ah, imagine.
Imagine.
Here we go.
Monstro two.
I don't think I've ever seen this guy.
This is new.
Unfortunately, I can't giant fart.
Oh, that hurts.
Oh, health.
I can barely pick up the items because they're so small.
It's funny.
Oh, I keep thinking my shield is going to keep me safe, but that's not how this works.
You like bombs?
Hehe.
The bombs are not doing that much damage, I will say that.
We're totally chilling, though.
Common calculated.
No reason to overreact.
We're totally just killing it right now.
My hands are steady.
I should have seen that coming.
Wait, why am I am I getting healed somehow?
How am I getting healed here?
Necropolis.
I don't understand what was happening half that fight.
Mom's underwear.
All right, we have plenty range.
It's just that we don't have any damage, right?
That's kind of funny.
But now, let's go north.
I'm going to jump.
That's fine, because I have the shield.
We're going to charge up the fart and use it somewhere smart.
We're going to go so hard.
There's a battery over there I could take.
What's this?
Unidentified?
Oh, I'm tempted.
Bad gas.
That's maybe good, maybe not.
Nobody knows.
Should I be giving this guy my one coin?
Okay, fine.
And he stole it.
Fantastic.
Okay, there's a big room.
Man, I can't kill enemies.
Utilize the range.
Utilize the range here.
Play it smart.
We're chilling.
My shield is blocking so much.
I mean, I'm purposefully just standing still here.
Wait, they're disappearing.
And the range is nice though.
That took a while to clear that.
Okay, we got an item here.
Some bomb thingy?
Explosivo.
Sticky bomb shot.
25% chance to fire a sticky tier that will grow and explode.
For 60 damage when attached to an enemy.
Oh, wait, with my normal shot.
And you're not saying with my bombs.
Oh, cool.
Amazing.
We're gonna get like 10,000 sources of healing by the end of this run.
This way.
But I have to see what that animation looked like.
Like, when is it happening, you know?
Uh-oh.
How can you...
How?
That's impossible to dodge.
Oh, bomb!
Did it heal me?
I don't know if it did.
Bomb?
Oh, it totally heals me, bro!
This is crazy!
This is like the tank build.
We do no damage, but we tank forever.
That's so cool.
What the heck?
Oh, we got super money in there.
I can't blow it up, though.
But wait, we have a tanked man!
Check this out!
Yoink!
Look at me go!
Smart!
Kill this guy.
No problem.
Oh, I should actually let them explode, I guess.
How come I couldn't pick that heart up?
I'll save it.
Did that heal me?
It's a little more trouble than anything else getting that healing.
But it's okay.
I have five keys, zero bombs.
We got to go back to the beginning and start exploring those rooms.
Also, I didn't pay attention.
Are we at the mom phase yet?
We may be, actually.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Jesus Christ, man.
That room is going to be the end of me.
We could give this guy more coins, but nah.
Heal me?
Batteries.
Oh, we have full fart!
The butt is ready to strike.
It's going to be an event for the ages when you see this guy go off.
Uh-oh.
Oh, god.
Dude, I take so much damage!
I'm trying here.
Okay, uh, blow this up.
Yay!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, what's up, guys?
I really want to use my poopy butt, but I'm not gonna.
All right.
Some enemies are actually harder to heal from, because they're just very scary close range.
Nice!
Look at me go.
So many rocks, there's got to be a sus one among these.
Wait, if I place a bomb here and blow this up, I wonder if that heals me for two.
Meaning, uh, one full heart.
Because my bomb, and then the thing in there.
Huh, huh?
Next level thinking.
But I don't have any bombs, so.
Rip!
Okay.
What else do we miss?
Okay, a couple rooms over here.
There's maybe mom, actually, that we're about to face.
I don't recall which floor we're on.
Whoa!
Um, hmm, maybe I'll do that.
I'll think about it.
What about all this poop?
I don't think that can drop, uh, money.
What is your special?
Fantastic.
Health?
Oh my god!
Really?
Magdalene!
You unlock challenges?
The tank!
What are the chances?
I said I was a tank!
Insanity.
I have actually unlocked my full potential here.
Should I donate?
Nah.
I'm not made of health, you know.
Let's get out of here.
Yep.
We got eight monies.
We could go to the store.
We also have the poopy butt.
That could be huge.
Somehow I completely nailed that just now.
Walked through it, no problem.
What was this?
This looks good!
Some kind of pouch.
Maybe it allows me to have two active items, or...
I don't even know what else would that do.
Maybe it allows me to have two in the bottom left.
This one is an unknown.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna save my money.
I'll save my money.
Okay, let's go.
It's boss time.
With no damage.
Oh, it is Mom!
Okay!
Well, there you go.
Wow.
Here's some bombs for you.
Oh, I have no bombs.
Oh.
Look at all the bombs I'm shooting in a row there.
Ouch.
Get out of there!
Nice.
Man, I deal so little damage.
Okay.
Yeah, what is it, Mom?
I'm busy.
Have some bombs.
Oh, man, they don't explode in time before she disappears.
That's too bad.
Ah, I should have seen that coming.
That was bad.
And this is a rough boss fight.
Blow me up.
Good.
Man.
Dude, I am so focused.
It's crazy.
I feel like I gotta have four eyes to do this.
Like, I gotta look on all the enemies and look for the shadow.
This is super hard for me.
Ah, man!
Wait, where am I?
I can't even see- Oh, I'm here!
I'm sucked out of the way!
I'm on the screen!
Fuck!
It's so over.
Okay, here she comes.
Good.
Wow.
Blow me up.
Yeah, good.
Good, good, good.
Oh, I'm taking so much damage.
Blow me up.
Nice.
I need to be blown up here.
Huge.
Mom, what is it?
Midnight snack!
Even more health!
No freak- Wait, what's that?
Look at this hole!
Look at that hole!
Oh my goodness.
Whoa!
Spider baby?
Minus tears?
Yeah, absolutely not.
Contagion.
First enemy killed in each room explodes on point- Oh, that's good!
That's good!
That's really good!
Holy shit!
Blow shit up!
Okay.
That's a heart over there.
What is even happening here?
Okay.
Thanks.
Okay, okay.
Wait, what the hell?
Oh, that crazy room!
Oh, bombs, bombs!
Oh, this is bad, isn't it?
It is nuts.
This is absolutely nuts.
Come here.
Man, I can't fucking shoot you!
Oh!
Yeah!
Very nice.
I'm fully healed!
Hey, I love it!
Wait, are you on my side?
What's happening?
Time has slowed?
The angel is not on my side!
Nope, Angel is evil.
What is going on?
Oh my fucking god!
Ew!
Holy crap.
Yeah, blow me up!
Oh, that's good.
Fantastic.
Where's the big guy?
Where the hell are you?
Three out of fifteen?
Huh?
Hey, come here!
Hello?
I mean, this is weird.
I get one hit in.
One hit in at a time.
Okay, okay, he has a bomb on him.
Hey!
Okay, we got...
Oh, what the frick?
Four!
Okay, dude, this is gonna be an insane room!
Hello?
Okay.
He's making things dark.
Yeah!
We got devil people.
Why didn't that hit me?
Why am I taking damage?
Oh, that was a lot of healing.
That was beautiful.
Blow me up.
Fantastic.
This is such a fun build.
Okay, he's down.
We got small dudes.
Yeah!
That's right!
Hey!
Kill them all!
This is awesome.
I'm tanking him!
Who cares?
I don't care!
Oh, shit.
Okay, lasers are bad.
Oh, okay, we gotta take care of the laser dude.
Absolutely.
Okay, I'm taking damage!
This ain't good.
We're in trouble.
Fuck all y'all.
Okay, let's pick up some HP here.
What is hitting me?
I'm taking damage from something I don't know what is.
There's some bombs on him.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ouch.
Oh, hell.
I don't even know what is happening!
Where's all my bombs at?
I'm not shooting any bombs.
There we go.
That was actually so unlucky.
Look at the floor, dude!
Looks like a freaking...
Oh, shit.
I can't think.
Okay, get out.
Nice, nice.
Looks like a goddamn Jackson Pollock painting.
Come on, bombs, bombs!
In the bombs!
No bombs?
Oh, I should have been closer.
It's a mistake.
Wait, what the hell is that?
Oh, I would have loved those explosions on me, though.
This is the guy that also jumps, right?
Oh, he's dead already?
Wow.
Headless horseman, dude?
I'm very low HP here.
The shield is putting in overtime.
Wait, is this guy throwing bombs?
I could have used that to heal.
Crap.
Oh, my god.
Fuck all y'all.
Huge.
Give me that.
We got a big fat guy.
Guess we gotta keep moving, then, because he jumps really quick here.
Blow me.
Nice.
That's big, that's big, that's big.
Yep, yep, yep.
Okay, okay.
Something is following me.
There you are.
Wow, he becomes a skeleton now?
What is even happening here?
This is insanity.
Oh, I'm slowed in that.
Nice.
This guy's back.
Wait, what's this over here?
The stars.
Hold on, what is that?
Teleport to the tre- No, absolutely not.
We're doing this here.
Why didn't that hit me?
Blow me up.
Nice, that didn't hit me.
Missing number.
Pencil.
Oh, that's good.
We like the pencil.
That was a crazy room.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Oh, okay.
So that's what that means when you enter there, huh?
All right.
The poopy bot is ready as well.
In case we need it.
Okay, what's- Oh, we're in the womb now.
Okay, first things first, we heal up.
Dammit.
Ah, bombs.
Why did it say bombs?
I mean, bombs.
Uh, we need this bomb.
Fuck.
Boink.
Huh?
What is happening?
Why am I here?
What just triggered that?
Getting hit with an ex- No, that's the healing.
Yeah, I have no idea.
I have no idea.
What's this?
Prayer card.
Plus one internal heart.
What is that?
Oh, it replaces my poopy bot.
Huh?
Plus one internal heart.
I mean, we're gonna try it.
Oh!
Oh, shit, okay.
I'll be back for this later.
Oh, wait, can I come back later?
Oh, man, poopy bot is so good.
This may be a one-trip to come here.
We can't come back, I don't think.
I mean, we have enough health already.
I like poopy bot.
Maybe we can come back.
Ah, doesn't look like it.
Too bad.
Uh, I could go in there if I had a bomb, but I don't.
That's a rip.
This is gonna be rough, though, because I actually- I don't have any damage.
I wonder if those explosions are gonna heal me.
Range- No.
That's not good.
This one was to the tre- Yeah, let's do it.
Treasure room, me.
That's not a treasure room!
What the fuck is this?
Lies!
No, I can't go there.
What is happening?
Oh, that's creepy as hell.
I mean, I can block all your shit.
I can duel you any day of the week.
Oh my god, I'm dying.
Heal me!
Nice.
I'm very low HP here.
I think this is the end, guys.
Uh, down here.
Sloth!
Wait, that's gonna heal me, isn't it?
Oh, yeah!
Come on, then!
Oh my god, they're so slow.
Come here.
Hey, this is so much fun!
What the fuck?
More.
More!
Low me up.
Oh, I didn't get to- Okay, what's this?
Bob's rotten head.
Reusable ranged bomb?
Let's Isaac throw a- What?
That's good, though, because I can do- Wait, how does it work?
Oh!
Oh, I equip it and then- Okay, I see, I see.
Very cool.
But wait a sec.
The poopy butt is also good.
Hmm, I don't know what's best, though.
I guess I'll pick up this if I need to heal, and then I'll go back to the other one.
Yeah, that sounds like a good deal.
Hey, let's crack a-lacking!
As boss?
Not yet.
What is that symbol on the map?
Inside of that room, something's going on.
Oh, this is the merry-go-round of bombs.
Oh,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's go in here.
Whoa, what a room!
Mega suspicious!
Nice.
I'm changing my whole playstyle because of the shield.
Hopefully I'm not getting used to it too much.
What am I taking damage from?
What is happening?
Hey, what's happening?
I don't know what's happening!
We're fucking dying to nothing!
What the fuck was that?
I have got no clue.
Uh, shit, go back up.
Oh, oh, I want that.
Pills!
Range, that's bad.
This is unknown, so it's good.
Yeah, speed up.
But it's not really good.
It's just going to speed up my death, pretty much.
That's what that's going to do.
Uh-oh.
I'm in danger.
I'm dead.
I'm back, but I'm dead.
It's over.
Man, that was a fun-ass run, though.
That was a really cool run.
You can't deny that one.
Okay.
Do I still want to play with Lazarus, though?
I guess so.
Yeah, let's do what we've had two amazing runs.
Let's go with Lazarus again.
I'm feeling it.
I'm in the Lazarus mode.
Oh, and he actually starts with no bombs and nothing, actually.
That is a downside.
What is that room?
That's the library!
Okay.
Not super exciting.
This time we got to find some damage, because I pretty much did no damage last time.
I'm surprised I even got as far as I did with that setup there.
Okay.
Not too shabby.
These guys are easy.
Ow!
Spoke too soon.
Yo, let's just go for the boss immediately.
The haunt.
I have to remember, I don't have a shield anymore.
I was just playing like I had a shield.
Okay, they're gone.
Now you're doing that stuff.
Okay, that's cool.
Keep it up, son.
Oh my god, I'm whiffing.
Huge!
Oh, please!
Man, that wasn't too good.
What is this?
Shot speed, chance of planetarium spawning.
I don't know what the planetariums are good for.
Joker.
Teleport to the devil or angel room.
Let's do it.
Ooh, we're in the devil room!
Upside down cross.
And bloody flower.
Hmm.
Ah, no.
What is that?
Guppy's tail.
Oh, is that the one that saves me from...
No.
Increases chance of chests as room clear rewards, but also increases chance of no reward at all.
That doesn't sound good at all!
That was like it changes nothing.
All in all.
What do I want?
This one takes two hearts?
I'm going to take it just to experiment, guys.
Wait, I don't have two hearts!
I don't have two hearts.
We can't do that.
Wait, how do I leave?
Oh, I see.
Okay, back.
Let's go down here.
We're going to find some HP and then we're going to take it.
I just need to have at least two hearts.
Three hearts, I guess, technically.
No taking damage.
Piece of shit.
Nice.
It's huge.
Do I want money?
I don't think so.
Oh my god!
What the frick is going on here?
It's not too bad, though.
This guy has a gravity on him.
Ah, this room is fine.
We're chilling.
Holy shit.
I have to get rid of the mindset that bombs heal.
I was tempted multiple times there to run into the bombs.
Uh, okay.
Hey, there we go.
I'm going to go try it now.
Oh, there's also this place.
Oh, no keys.
Shit.
But I can go in here.
I'm an idiot.
That requires a key.
Oh, well, wait, where's the, uh, where's the devil room?
What's this?
Oh, nice.
Wait, where did the devil room go?
Huh?
Wait, I'm so confused.
Did it disappear?
Shit.
Oh, well.
This is probably better anyway.
Oh, crack jacks.
That's HP.
In fact, any food is HP.
Wait, what?
Lost cork?
Increase the sizes of Isaac's creep puddles.
Okay, okay.
We need keys, damn it.
We need those keys real bad.
Oh, there's a key.
There's also room down here.
What is that?
Rotten tomato!
Delicious?
I don't think so.
Chance to fire special tiers that apply a bait effect to enemies.
The bait effect slows enemies and draws other nearby enemies to attack them instead of Isaac.
Chance increases with luck.
Okay.
Well, the problem is with Lazarus, we have no luck.
We are perpetually unlucky.
Are we drooling?
Messed up.
Let's not go in there.
Actually go in there.
Okay.
Not too exciting.
Come here, guys.
Not a high chance of throwing that red thingy.
That was one.
Okay, we got rainbow?
What does it mean?
At least we're rich now.
Am I taking damage?
No, okay.
Something opened.
Oh, was it the door behind me?
I think so.
Okay.
Now, let's go to...
I guess we just leave.
No, we go to the library.
There's also a couple coins here, but I can't really reach them.
Oh, I wanted to go to the store as well, actually.
You can do that after.
What's this one?
Reusable item generator?
What?
Bookworm spawns a random pickup.
Whoa.
What the fuck?
That sounds really good!
Whoa!
Hello?
That sounds broken as hell.
Okay, with 12 coins.
Sharp key.
Plus five keys.
We can consume a key.
Enemies killed by the key.
Have a chance to drop pickups.
Or a pedestal item reward.
Okay, that I didn't realize.
That last one seems insane.
No, it replaces!
Maybe this one's better.
I like this one more.
I like the key.
Oh, yeah.
I walked into it!
This is a disaster!
Motherfucker.
Wait, where's the...
Where the fuck was that room I was in here?
I don't understand.
I think I can't access it anymore.
It's somewhere off, you know, in the distance.
Of course we walk in here.
Ah, that's spiky!
Whatever.
No!
Prevents active items from spawning.
Yeah, fuck active items.
Oh, wait, what's this?
The court gets replaced.
Yeah, fuck the creep puddles.
No two active items.
I have all the active items I need.
In fact, uh, wait, how did I use it again?
Oh, wait, space, of course.
Oh, oh, okay, so we equip it and then we throw.
Didn't drop anything.
Come here, come here, you motherfucker.
Amazing!
Aw.
Okay.
Dammit.
Aw, spiders?
I don't like that.
Oh, item down here.
What is that?
Infestation, fly revenge?
Spawn two to six blue flies whenever Isaac takes damage.
I don't want to take damage.
I hate those types of items.
Then again, I mean, I will take damage, right?
Whoa.
Is it always diagonal?
Okay, it is.
That means it's easy.
Let's try and kill this guy with a key.
We're gonna bring him low and kill him with a key.
Whoa.
Maybe there's a high chance he dropped something good because he's like a boss.
Or mini boss, whatever.
Okay, here we go.
Shit.
Didn't really drop anything special.
Okay.
Half the time, I'm like playing the game while looking at the minimap, you know?
It's like Starcraft.
Half my eye is on the minimap when I'm moving between rooms.
One eye on the minimap, the other one on the middle of the screen.
We're gonna gamble a little bit here.
Dang it.
I always want to keep at least one eye.
I mean, one key.
So I can open a chest or whatever, right?
Stop spawning that.
Okay, so it's always diagonal.
No, no, I mean, not the opposite of diagonal.
That was good.
Pheromones?
I feel like that's bad.
That's probably something like...
enemies are more attracted to me or something.
Okay, I don't want any of this.
I could buy a heart later if I really need it, but...
not super tempted to do it.
Ooh, I want that.
Okay.
Not too shabby.
Oh, yikes.
Dude, I'm dying in here.
Wait, at least that guy's gone.
Ooh, man.
Pills.
I need it.
Oh, huge.
Now I just need some healing.
And then we're cracking.
Cracker lacking.
Oh, god.
Oh, god, no keys.
What a disaster.
Man, I don't want to leave that behind.
I guess I have to.
Okay, wish me luck.
Ah, it's the duga flies.
Everything's fine.
No problem.
The little guy needs to die, though.
This guy is really annoying.
Oh, yeah, no problem.
Wait, some of these flies are bigger than the others.
Oh, two items.
This one is good.
Oh, no, I get to choose.
Oh, well, I misunderstood that.
I was going to pick the other one, then, just to see what it was, but whatever.
Eat the candy.
And then produce some creep.
Oh, man, I need keys.
My whole build is revolving around keys right now.
Which sounds really dumb, but somehow it's true.
And we have the butt flies.
The butt flies separated into individual cheeks.
Bro, I'm getting so much HP.
How about some healing?
That's what I really want.
There's also black shits in here.
Forgot what that was.
It's kind of hard to get to these guys.
Hit him.
Oi!
That was close.
We're going to have a field day with these chests, and we finally get keys.
Maybe these will have keys.
Makes it dark?
You saw that?
What is happening?
Okay.
Come here.
I'm not understanding the red shots I have.
They don't seem very good at all.
Like, they do nothing.
At least it doesn't feel like it.
Okay.
Let me see that again.
I need to read it.
Let's see here.
Chance to fire special tears that apply a bait effect.
It slows enemies and draws other nearby enemies to attack.
Really?
I don't notice that at all.
Huh.
Oh, wow.
Let's try and see.
Are they attacking them?
Okay, they are.
There you go.
Kill them.
Nice.
Get them.
I'm getting lots of bombs, but where's my keys?
My chests as well.
It's actually a tragedy.
Kill each other.
Is it just me or is my damage atrocious?
Lazarus is not very good with damage.
And once again, I need keys.
It's insane.
Oh, man.
There are so many chests just waiting for me.
Focus.
Why are they not shooting me anymore?
Okay, they are.
Fucking look at the map.
Look how many chests there are.
I just keep taking damage here.
Oh, my God.
Fucking get out of here.
You gotta be kidding me.
Fuck!
Wow.
This run is so over.
I just want to restart, man.
This is absolutely horrendous.
I'm also in the corner now.
I'm dead.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fucking start it over.
Eight chests and no keys.
It's insane.
Fucking crazy luck.
Unbelievable stuff.
Just run it back.
Start over.
Oh, not the poopy man.
Get away from me, poopy man!
Mom's wig.
Wait, what was that?
Heels red hard.
Firing has a chance to spawn blue spiders.
Okay, okay.
That's decent.
And it looks kind of stylish, too.
I'm feeling it.
This wig will produce a victory.
There's no way it cannot.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, that was a chain reaction.
Thanks.
I kind of want to experiment with those rooms a bit more.
Oh, fucking bumps!
Jesus.
Okay, no, no, no.
Now we don't do it because we lost HP.
This way.
Ah, bro.
I'm stuck in the corner.
Playing so bad.
Just fuck up my shit, okay?
Just start over again.
It's over.
Run it back.
Okay, he's dead.
Oh, what a shot, though.
Fantastic.
Run it back!
Start the shit over!
Like, it doesn't get worse than this.
It cannot get worse.
Uh, what was in here?
What is that one?
One plus one equals exclamation mark.
All right, let's do the boss.
Ah, I was hoping for duke of lies.
This is going to be difficult, I think.
Yeah, they're going to charge.
I think I can do it.
Not looking good.
I'm half hoping that I'm dying, actually.
Okay.
Tropicamite.
That's good.
I don't think I found a single damage up item in the last three hours I've been playing.
Like, it's crazy.
Wait, we just lost a bunch of stats.
Why is that?
Dogbone.
A snack.
Okay, that's good.
We got the HP back.
We needed that.
Got a little devil over there.
What do you think you are, huh?
Wait, what if I jump in that hole?
Oh!
Oh, cool.
What a neat boss!
Or mini boss.
He's the demon of portals.
Ah, wait, there you are.
It's not that bad, though.
Like, it's not too bad.
Whoa.
Oh, there's just to get that little dog treat, huh?
Ah!
Oh!
He's so cute, though!
I just want to pinch his cheeks.
Oh, no.
No, no, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Oh, he's crying now.
What a cutie.
We have a problem, though.
Because we're about to die.
Oh!
You
got to stack them up.
That's the way to do it.
Sir, would you mind coming over here?
Your turn to die.
No room reward.
Oh, man.
Oh, boy.
Coin me.
Where did that guy come from?
Oh, it was mine.
I thought it was an enemy.
Unidentified pill.
Let's take it.
There we go.
Cheers up.
That's something.
That's a type of damage increase.
We're in trouble.
We still have a resurrect.
Let's not forget.
So it's not the end of the world.
Oh, no.
This is the worst.
Come on.
Die.
Thank you.
Okay.
Needed.
That one is the one that spawns a random thing, right?
No, that's a damage nullifying shield.
Okay.
I see.
We may have to utilize that here.
But only if shit hits the fan.
And so far, the shit is nowhere near the fan.
It is definitely in the same room, though.
In the corner, there's a little poop spot.
But just you see, any moment now, that poop will start to move all on its own.
As if magic.
And it will slowly approach the fan.
It's devilish.
And then I gotta be ready.
It's not me that's obsessed with poop, by the way.
This game is obsessed with poop, okay?
I'm just, you know, on the same wavelength right now.
There's my healing!
Frickin' fantastic.
Very good.
It was so over, and now we're actually so back.
Funny how that works.
Oh.
Come here.
Ah, that's unfair.
I was waiting in ambush.
Little monster.
I can't believe this wig we're wearing.
It is so silly looking.
Wait, oh, there.
Spiders.
Yeah, the red chests are kinda...
bad.
Like, half the time, they spawn enemies.
Ah, there's a coin store.
Um...
Nah, I don't like...
Oh, I can do this.
Wait, it didn't do anything.
Oh, okay, you need a couple more tries.
Jar of flies.
That's a blue fly to the jar for each enemy kill.
Maximum 20 flies can be stored.
Using the jar releases all flies.
Okay, I want a pill.
Let me guess, it's gonna be a lemon party.
Well, now we are definitely the unluckiest person in the world.
It's going to be bombs in every chest and the worst enemies and whatever else luck is affecting in this game.
I can only assume it's pretty much everything.
The haunt.
Wow, they died fast.
Okay, there we go.
It's kinda disgusting the way he pulls his foreskin back when he starts shooting, you know?
Wow, that was close.
Look at me, I'm nailing all the shots.
Whoa!
Okay, I missed there.
We got him.
Hell yeah.
And some HP.
Yeah, baby.
All right.
Man, we're being suffocated in the chest.
We did not have a great upbringing here, did we?
Oh, oh, not this.
I'm actually kind of good at it though.
Oh, oh, oh.
Master gamer.
It is I.
Kill it!
Okay, okay.
We're totally chilling, we're chilling.
Did those guys just collide?
Oh, it was one of mine, okay.
Oh, there's pills and stuff over there.
I could get in here.
That's actually worth it.
Ow!
The tower.
You know what?
Maybe we can use that somewhere to blow up things.
I just realized the genius tactic with this thing.
Wait, we also had an active.
What was that?
Oh, we had the damage nullifying shield.
Blow it up.
Where are those tomatoes?
Wow, that's so tough to dodge.
Okay.
Jesus Christ, it's impossible.
Oh, I legit thought that was a tomato I could pick up again.
I don't know what it is about me.
These things look like such delicious tomatoes.
I just want to eat them.
Shield me!
I need it bad right now.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, they die fast, huh?
Okay, so it's definitely when I clear a room, I get more mana.
Ugh!
I didn't damage it.
Ew, these guys are disgusting.
There's a room I missed.
And a pill, too.
Ah, but that's the pill on the little place I can't access.
This way.
What a suspicious room, though.
Something's up with those fires.
Oh, I'm not.
Ah, man, don't do this to me.
Okay, they shoot straight.
Okay,
not too bad, actually.
Somehow, I'm still alive.
Oh, no way.
So lucky.
Secret room.
Huge.
Of course.
What else did I expect?
I feel like luck is like a super important stat.
Oh, man.
Wow, what a dodge.
Ah, this thing.
Battery pack.
Fully recharges the health active item.
It's not that great, is it?
Let's start donating.
I'm gonna fill this thing up.
111, by the way, is the amount we have in the dono box.
Oh, wait, there's a weird room up here.
Hey!
Bump friend, he's greedy.
Familiar that collects coin pick-ups and occasionally pays out with pick-ups, triggers, or items.
Are you gonna pick it up from you over there?
Oh, my god!
That is so cool.
Let's see if we have any more like that.
There's also room here that I cannot access, but we can go in there, but that's a bad idea.
Except I can put on the damage shield.
Not worth.
It's too risky.
I'm way too risky.
I think it's time for the boss.
This shouldn't be too hard.
Gertie Jr., we also have the damage shield.
Fuck!
Okay, put it on.
It may be very hard.
What was the tower?
Troll bombs.
Let's do it.
Enjoy that one!
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, buddy!
Blue Cap is a fun guy.
Tears, shot speed, health.
Nice.
Let's go.
So, wait, we're gonna get 1 extra health now, right?
Because of the silver heart.
Yeah!
Okay, cool.
Pretty much confirmed, then, how that works.
Oh, god!
What the fuck!
This room!
It's impossible!
How's anyone...
Nah, nah, bro.
Okay, just keep going back and forth.
That works.
Hey, okay, okay!
That wasn't too bad, actually, huh?
I totally overreacted there.
The Empress, more damage.
I need to start using it, too.
It's space.
Bum friend, do you mind helping out a little bit here?
Do the dishes, perhaps?
Okay, I have good damage, though.
Like, this is a difference between now and before.
It's not fantastic, but it's good.
Well, compared to before, anything is good, right?
Okay, okay.
This guy's gonna shoot as well.
Ow!
Unbelievable.
He just spit out a coin.
Incredible.
How do I even dodge?
I can't.
Play it safe.
Holy crap.
Oh.
Oh, I could have used a shield here.
No!
Oh, my God!
These enemies are so difficult.
Wow.
Oh, man.
I'm in shambles.
Wait, it's a mini-duka fly.
Got him.
Okay.
We got the shield.
So now we can do this.
Lovely!
What a strategy.
I'm gonna frickin' die.
Play it safe.
Oh, man.
I need HP.
I mean, yeah.
I feel like there's nothing I can do there.
Wait, how did I just kill him?
He was in his configuration where he couldn't take damage.
Do I have some kind of ability to shoot through that?
I don't think so.
Oh, crap.
Capricorn.
All stats up.
Oh, sick!
Whoa!
Not gonna be of much use, though, if I can't.
Oh, wait, never mind.
I have healing.
Greed.
I just can't dodge those frickin' projectiles.
Bull the hell games are my ultimate weakness in all of gaming.
What's this one?
Oh, Steam Sail.
Cool.
Praise the Gaben.
For he has once upon a time decided that he should bless us.
And he did.
He spoke the words, and the games were cheap.
Good times were had.
Oh, shit.
If I'm far away, I can dodge it.
But if I'm close, no shot.
At least I'm doing pretty good damage here.
My damage is respectable.
I like the damage.
I'm gonna blow this fucker up.
Yeah.
Hoi, buddy.
Another Empress.
All right, don't mind if I do.
Trying to draw them in the corner and then walk away.
Corral them.
Oh, oh, can you collect the coin?
Come here, come here, guy.
Collect some for me.
Thanks for the pooping.
The way he was animated, it looked like he pooped out the little bomb.
That was cute.
I want to go to this room up here.
Little, little lamp.
Oh, I also have a shield.
Don't forget the spaghetti.
Yep, the boo-boo.
Bond time.
I mean, boss time.
Mega fatty.
You're so fat.
How fat you are.
Oh!
Not bad.
Nailed it.
Torn photo.
More tears.
Wait, tears means damage, right?
No, that's attack speed and shot speed.
Okay, okay, got it, got it.
Oh, my God, look at this.
Look at that.
Look at it.
Oh, yeah.
We're crying so hard.
We're going to cry a river.
I feel so bad for Isaac.
Every time I see those movies, I just want to cry with them.
That's the new music.
Oh, no, not the purple stuff.
Oh, my God, it's so crazy, the purple.
I didn't mean to go in here.
It was a mistake.
They're invisible.
I access this place by mistake.
What the fuck, dude?
Ocular rift.
Oh, that's the black hole, isn't it?
Chance to fire tears that summon a rift where they land.
The rift lasts for two seconds, pulling pickups and enemies towards them and dealing rapid contact damage to enemies.
Chance increases with luck.
What is the other one?
I mean, my luck is shit, so it's not going to be good for me.
I want to try this.
The Book of Belial.
Temporary...
What was that?
Gain damage up for the current room.
Passively increases devil angel room chance.
Oh, that's what those numbers on the left mean.
The higher that number is, the higher the chance of getting one of these rooms.
I think I get it now.
That makes sense.
So wait, what do you mean passively?
When does it trigger, though?
Gain damage up for the current room.
Bookworm two out of three!
What happens when we get another one?
Oi, yo, yo.
I'm going to leave that.
It's too risky.
Wait, where am I?
Oh, I was so confused because I left north and then I arrived here, so I have to go back here.
We got good damage now, now we just gotta dodge.
Man, attack speed is so nice.
It helps a ton.
This way.
What is this dramatic music, though?
Nice.
That guy was pooping.
I'm liking this run so far.
Uh, blasting cap.
Bombs have a 10% chance to spawn a bomb on detonation.
Uh...
Okay, sure.
Why not?
Sloth.
This is the lazy guy.
Oh man, the damage is good.
Justice.
Whoa.
Spawns one hard key bomb.
Whoa, okay.
Sweet.
Oh!
That was not a friendly bomb.
Let's not forget the Empress.
We're gonna save that for a really hard...
Let's save it for the mom.
The mom.
Yeah, I have a bad feeling about this.
This is good.
Okay, okay.
What's happening here?
It's not too bad, honestly.
They can keep pooping all they want.
Wait, can they not move through the spikes?
Oh yeah, they stop moving when the spikes come up.
Okay, that's good to know.
See ya!
What is this?
Drops one lit bomb per second for five?
Oh no, no, no.
I mean, that could be good, actually.
Depending on when you use it and what you use it for.
Oh, this is gonna be a rough one, isn't it?
Ah, it's not that bad, actually.
There we go.
Oh, it's so hyped with the music!
It's like an action flick.
Lazarus.
In theater this summer.
There will be poop.
Emergency, what was that?
Contact!
Help from above.
Response to mom's hands to damage and pin enemies?
Whoa!
That's pretty cool.
Not the purple guys.
Okay, I'm doing pretty well.
Nice!
Jesus Christ.
That was wild.
Explosive diarrhea would be good here.
I'm imagining neighbor listening to this.
What the fuck is he playing, you know?
Okay, I think I'll keep the one I have.
The emergency contact.
No, no, no, I like this more.
It's gonna amplify more with my attack speed.
It will actually be better, trust.
Oh, it's bomb spiders!
Kill them all!
Okay, oh, that's the boss.
Not yet.
What's the points?
Oh yeah, he grabs coins!
I need to remember that.
Now poop something, yeah!
Fantastic.
There's a couple of rooms I want to do.
I'm trying to think, is it always a smart idea to clear the entire stage?
I think it is, because you want as many chances at items and pickups as possible, right?
Uh-oh.
Okay, that works.
No!
Like, how could I avoid that?
Okay, that's all.
But, I mean...
Yo, okay.
What is that?
Looks like a meaty flower.
Giant cell, micro friends.
Taking damage spawns a mini familiar that chases and attacks enemies.
These mini familiars last until destroyed from taking enough damage.
Max of 16 at a time!
Damn!
That's a lot.
Okay, come on, Lazarus.
Find something good now.
Oh, my fucking god, bro!
Yeah, this room is crazy.
Thanks.
I must have another heart somewhere.
Yeah, I do.
Oh, there's a room over here.
Time for the boss!
Actually, we do have a couple of monies we can potentially spend.
I don't want to go that way, that's too risky.
I want to spend some money here.
I'm here.
Also,
what was this active we had?
Taking damage up to the current room passively.
Oh, yeah, right.
I wonder if that passively thing only happens when I click the thing.
What's this?
Unidentified?
Oh, I'm tempted.
I like the pills.
Bad trip.
Yeah, that's not good.
This was bad.
I'll buy this.
That was horrible.
I'm gonna donate.
It's broken.
I donated too much?
Or what?
Maybe I'm too broken.
I'm gonna take this, and then we go boss.
I'm gonna use the book Mask of Infamy.
Oh, wait, we shoot the heart, I guess?
Oh, god.
Wow!
This thing is crazy!
Look at my little mini-mes!
We got an army!
Come on, brothers and sisters!
Kill him!
Get him out of here!
Why is he only taking damage sometimes?
Weird.
Wait, I can go grab more.
What's this?
Mom's lipstick.
Sick range.
Sponsored red heart.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
Let's go!
So far, so good!
This is looking promising!
We got a disgusting purple guy here!
Hate these guys.
My damage is starting to feel less impressive.
That took a while.
Here.
God, I hate this lipstick look.
The range is good.
Always want to go in here.
What do we have here?
Cricket's head.
Is that someone I know?
That's a lot of damage!
Whoa!
Brother!
That is a crazy amount!
Just when I said we were running low on damage.
Oh yeah, that's what I'm talking about, baby.
That's what I'm talking about.
I can't get in there.
I keep thinking my familiars are enemies!
Three coins.
Minus one luck.
Maybe if you get to minus ten luck, you actually get the plus 20 luck.
Like, if you're too unlucky, maybe the game is like, okay, you know what?
Throw my bone.
Kind of want to see, though, what happens when you get to mega infinity luck.
What the...
I almost died.
Empty chest?
No.
Just shoot him.
My range is nuts.
Hold on, these rocks look a little...
weird.
No, they're fine.
That's a red one!
It's gone.
Oh!
Damn!
We need healing.
This is getting a little ridiculous.
Let's go find some.
Oh god, I'm scared of that.
Oh no!
It's fine!
We're okay.
We got black poop.
Makes it darker.
Huh?
Mom's on the...
Oh!
We're gonna get three out of three!
What does it mean?
Mom's contact has appeared.
Wait, what?
Mom's underwear spawns three to six blue flies on pickup.
What is that knife?
I'm holding a knife.
Wait.
What is doing that?
Heals one red heart.
Maybe that collects coins.
It's gotta be the three out of three on the mother.
That gave me a knife?
Or what?
Capricorn.
Whoa, this one does a lot.
Okay.
Yeah, it's gotta be the three out of three.
Shit.
Oh no, this is scary!
Uh...
Wow.
Wait, what was my active?
Damage.
We need healing now.
All the healing we can get.
No, not keys.
Oh wow.
Oh wait, this is a bad idea.
Oh no, it gives me healing.
It's a good idea.
Use it!
Damage me!
We're going mega damage.
We're going Empress as well!
Appear!
You bastard!
Oh, okay.
Calm down, calm down.
He's dead though, he's dead.
Oh, totally worth.
Totally worth.
Sick.
Oh, there's a...
Ooh!
Nice!
Freaking fantastic.
Dude, shooting so fast is so much fun!
I think I almost like this more than Azazel now when I shoot this fast.
This is great.
Okay, but now it's time for the boss.
Oh my god, that's so scary.
We could go up there.
Ooh, should we?
Should we?
Fuck those fires!
We're going, we're going.
Boss time, let's go.
Oh man, they always shoot me when I least expect it.
It's Mom?
I thought we were two levels away from that!
They were doing a lot of damage here though, this is great.
Ow!
That hurt.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I nailed that, didn't I?
Freaking nailed that.
Latchkey!
The much needed luck.
Thank you.
Okay, now.
Oh, we can't go back anyway.
Okay, here we go.
Wish me luck.
We're thinking about stars and...
Oh, right.
That is so evil.
Even the clouds.
Wow!
The range, though, makes it so that it can dodge much easier.
I can shoot them off-screen!
Wait, what is this following me?
Oh.
Something was following me there.
Whoa!
Nice!
The fool.
Teleport to the starting room.
Actually, yes!
We can use that here.
Wait, oh.
We got enemies.
Truck cloth.
No, turret cloth.
What is turret cloth?
Doubles the effects of most cards.
Wait, how would you double the effect of a teleport?
And drops a card on pickup.
Deals 80 damage in the room.
That's pretty cool.
I like that.
Wait, that's gonna be 160, then.
160 damage.
Wait, oh no.
Now I can't Levi this, though.
I'm gonna take this and leave.
I think it's worth.
How come I took a full heart of damage there?
What the frick, man?
I was supposed to take half a heart of damage.
What the fuck is that?
That's new.
I gotta be on my toes now.
This ain't the basement anymore.
We're in the womb, or whatever.
Uterus...
Something.
Now we go down.
Well, I can't go in there.
Can I?
Is this wobble?
Well, that's... yeah, okay.
Oh, that's huge.
Give me that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oi!
How is everyone so incredibly different?
Like, every single run is a different game.
But it's gonna thin out at some point.
I mean, I feel like I found so many items already.
I think I'm, you know, getting there.
I'm not gonna say I find all the items, but maybe half?
Look at that!
Wow, that was close.
Nice.
Easy.
Okay.
Actually, I saw poop in there.
I should have gone for that.
Whoa!
I need the poop.
I requires the poop.
I have good damage.
This is good damage.
Lots of bombs, too.
The boss is here.
No way, bro.
Not yet.
There's a couple rooms I need to explore first.
What is this symbol in here?
Oh, the slot machine.
No, thanks.
I'm just sniping them on the other side of the freaking screen here.
He's very tactical, this guy.
He's hiding behind the thingies.
Beautiful.
I have a crazy room.
I don't know what this knife does that I have.
Maybe it does damage enemies when you get close to them.
I haven't seen it, though.
Poop out something for me.
Actually, I should let this guy collect all the coins.
Like, I should not be collecting it.
Even if I can.
Ow, ow, ow.
No, Scotland?
10% chance to fire a booger that sticks to enemies for 10 seconds and deals Isaac's damage once per sec.
Ooh.
50% chance for the booger to be homing.
That is insane.
Oh, wait, it replaced...
Ah, whatever.
The other one sucked ass, right?
We don't want that.
Who cares?
Let's not forget, we also have a death card.
That should come in handy.
Look at that booger.
It's green and gooey.
The booger sounds really good against bosses.
He has a booger on him.
Why is nothing happening?
He can't die?
Oh, wait, I need to wait, maybe?
Ah, there we go.
Okay, okay.
Spawn's hearts, I guess.
Very needed.
Very thank you.
Great English there.
Okay, I should not attack him.
Man, it's hard not to attack them.
There we go.
Open up your mouth.
Thank you.
Open up!
I dare you to open your mouth!
Look at that booger!
The booger strikes again.
Fantastic.
Are you gonna poop for me?
No pooping for me.
Let me think.
What is the optimal way to do this?
Probably like here.
No!
I thought it would hit one on both sides!
Shitballs!
Okay, well.
Let me in.
What is this pill?
Puberty?
What does that do?
I mean, other than the obvious signs of puberty.
Deeper voice, perhaps.
A bit of hair on the old peepee.
A tiny voice crack, perhaps?
Yep.
Wow!
I nailed that!
I was just sitting there in the corner shooting my shit, you know?
Sick.
Wait, what?
Oh, he gave me something else.
Have fun with that.
What is this thing?
Unfair, unfair.
Man, oh man!
What is this?
Oh, I can't read it!
Paperclip?
Wait, where?
Oh!
Lock chest can be opened without using...
That's kind of cool!
I like that, but I like this one more, I think.
Uh, this heart right here is massive.
I'm gonna take it, I think.
And then, I'm excited.
Oh wait, I should have taken it after killing the boss.
Whoops, I just made a big old doogie.
Yeah.
We're gonna have to not take damage on this boss.
Now, actually, we can take a little bit of damage.
A tiny bit.
Just a tiny bit.
What does my active do again?
Why do I keep forgetting about that?
Those are something down here.
Oh, you're right, this thing.
Oh wait, I need my, uh, I forgot my fucking 160.
We need 160.
I'm happy that I'm fast.
Fast as fuck, boy!
Oh, I'll run into that.
Yuck!
The thing is, though, I don't know how much 160 is, really.
Because there's no health bars or anything, no numbers.
So it's just a random number to me.
But I assume it's good.
The thing is, though, it's AoE.
Maybe not as good as you'd think.
Against a single enemy, I mean.
What a huge ass level!
Look at this!
Isn't that one of the biggest levels ever?
This has to be the biggest level I've ever been in.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Daddy long legs!
What the hell?
That's a new one.
Activate the book!
You like, you like that?
Oh god.
Oh, we can hit the legs.
I see.
Wait, I can just stay down here.
Can't hit me, it seems.
Whoa!
Plot Claude.
Plus one damage and more range for Isaac's left eye.
Whoa, nice.
Huge.
And we...
Oh, dude.
We kept a little extra heart, too.
We're gonna get an upgrade.
Now it's mom time.
We will not forget.
Yeah, nice.
Wait, what?
Oh, you bastard!
How dare you surprise me like that?
Fucking hell.
Oh, I can't get in there.
Do I look like a Zazel?
Enjoy my snot.
Bastard.
Oh, those are friends.
Now we go right.
Uh-oh.
Mom!
She's gonna stomp her feet.
Oh, a brand new dance.
Oh, wait, I don't understand this room.
That made no sense just now.
May you find all you have lost?
What was that?
Teleports.
Ooh!
Yeah!
Money!
Wait, that's an enemy.
Or not.
Oh!
Oh, it's right here!
That's funny.
Give me that back.
Uh, yeah, this way.
Oh, god.
Oh, that's...
Oh, no!
Fuck that shit!
That's horrible.
I want that.
Ooh, we're low on HP here.
He didn't even do anything!
All right.
Sure.
Uh, ooh, I want this one up here.
I'm gonna take this one, too.
Lovely.
Don't get affected.
Oh, god damn it.
Uh, wait, this guy's gonna...
No, he's not gonna collect things for me.
No.
What is that pill?
I don't think I wanna know.
If I can't get it anyway.
Fuck!
I swear to god, that room is killer!
It's impossible not to take damage in there.
Frickin' gravity bullshit.
Huh?
How did I just die?
What?
I have no idea how I just died.
That was random as fuck.
All right.
Ooh.
No way!
That is amazing.
Oh, no, it's broken.
I can't use it.
That is so unfortunate.
Do we have a proper money room here?
Doesn't look like it.
Okay, why is this room weird?
Okay, there's nobody here.
Shit.
Oh, god.
Oh, yeah, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
We're chilling.
33 coins, man.
Insanity.
Gimme.
Stapler.
Damage up!
Even...
Dude, I have a lot of damage.
What the fuck?
Peace.
This is where all the damage items went, the other run I was asking for them.
They were waiting for me in this run.
No.
I can't even get to it, though.
Maybe I can with bombs.
Ah, fuck!
I also take damage.
For some reason, I was still in...
I can tank bombs mode, but I can't.
A pill?
Question mark?
A pretty fly?
I don't know what that means.
What does that do?
Kill them all.
Kill them, kill them, kill them.
I took damage somehow.
I'm not sure how.
Oh, man.
We are so close to done here.
You know that, right?
Oh, no, it's over.
It's over.
I'm using everything I can.
We can't take any damage.
No way!
Oh, yeah!
Let's see that bottom of yours!
Cheeks!
Yeah!
Oh!
Huh?
What did we just find?
That was so horrific.
Wow.
Dude, the damage at the end was nuts.
All the boogers stacking, dealing damage per second.
Oh, my God.
That was a crazy run.
Wasn't this also the run where I started with one HP at some point?
I was like, it's over.
Run it back.
Wow.
Holy shit.
Damn.
The rubber cement has appeared.
Okay, that's what I unlocked.
Raft baby?
Guys, that was it for this time.
What a way to end it.
What a way to end that.
Absolutely incredible.
Now, I'm going to spend the next 20 minutes pretending to respond to people in the chat, because this is, of course, a pre-recorded video.
Thank you.
Yes, I am very good.
I appreciate it.
You too, Mr. Ryan in the chat.
I'm kidding.
Oh, man.
You get $50 from me.
So much that...
Wasn't that a crazy run?
Unbelievable.
This game is...
Yeah, Diego.
Absolute cinema is right.
That's what this game is.
You start from nothing.
I was at one HP, baby.
And then we ended up where we were.
From zero to hero, literally.
The most unbelievable run.
Fuck, this is so addicting.
We're going to need to have a stream ASAP.
Another stream ASAP.
This is...
You guys weren't kidding.
This is truly crack for adults and kids alike, I guess.
I don't have any color blindness, Frank.
I have taken color blindness tests.
I aced them all.
I mean, I can take one right now.
To prove it.
You've seen 1% of the game?
No, I haven't.
No way.
You're definitely overreaching with that statement.
Even if you were somewhat right, you're not right.
There's no way I've seen 1%.
Okay, 5% I can buy.
But even then, I'm questioning that.
That sounds almost not true.
I can't believe that.
They might be right?
No way.
What do you mean?
It's four...
I don't even know what that means.
It's 4% on God?
I think 6% is reasonable.
Yeah, that would maybe be...
I mean, now you also low balled it or high balled it, however you want to look at it, by seeing 1%.
So now everything except that sounds like a lot, right?
Honestly, I would have thought maybe 20%, 30%.
Like in terms of content, you know?
I'm talking content here, guys.
Not like, you know, secrets and all that or whatever.
I don't believe you.
Okay, whatever.
I guess we'll see, won't we?
Aren't secrets...
Yeah, I mean, they are, I guess.
But yeah, you're right.
Secrets are content, true.
Angel or devil?
Obviously, angel.
We don't like devils here.
Demons are...
the worst.
We don't like demons.
I am a good guy.
I am on the right side of the law here.
There's no demon business.
I'm not, I'm not a demon.
I know you guys like to think I am, but I'm not.
You got it all wrong.
I'm the guy that points out demons.
I know how to spot them, okay?
But I'm not a demon myself.
What did you think of the boss rush?
Are you talking about the big room with the 15 stages?
I loved it.
Wasn't that a crazy fight?
With the healing and the bombs?
The sustainability?
That was insane.
CTK, I'm from Denmark.
That was unbelievable.
Can't believe you won that, me neither.
It was so close to being over.
Hundreds of times during that.
That was the run where I had almost no damage as well.
Like, it took forever.
It was just a survive situation.
Can you speak Deutsch?
Yeah, I can speak Deutsch.
But I'm not gonna speak German now.
Entire stream was basically, we're so bad, it's so over at infinitum.
Yeah, I agree.
Honestly, I've had pretty good runs today.
Even the first two runs I had were pretty good.
Right?
Like, those runs were fun as hell.
Even though I didn't win.
Uh, genius France, I do not even remember the boss rush music.
I was so in it, I have no recollection of it at all.
Maybe I noticed it while playing, but I don't remember it now.
I guess I'll see it again when I get to that point again.
I know three languages, Cordy Lam.
English, German, Danish.
Favorite item so far?
Oh, that's a good question.
What is my favorite item?
Oh, it's gotta be...
I like the laser.
The run I had with the laser, that was too much fun.
Either that or the circle thingy.
The laser circle.
I don't recall what the name of that item was, but yeah, that one.
Technology, was that the name of it?
Hello from Kazakhstan, contradictory to nickname.
Why is your nickname genius France, then?
That's a bit weird.
Oh yeah, hello.
Reading from Denmark.
Yeah, hi, we just passed 140k on YouTube.
It's crazy.
I still can't believe we're over 100k.
It's insanity.
My artist has a song named Genius in France.
Love it.
Oh, okay.
I see.
Are you gonna do the challenges in game?
Yeah, at some point.
I kind of like challenge things in games.
Like under a circle, or like doing things with a certain limitation or something like that.
But I mean, I feel like I don't need challenges right now.
I'm struggling as it is, with the standard gameplay.
So maybe when I get better at the game, is when I'm gonna start doing the challenges.
The challenges could get pretty challenging.
Yeah, that's what I assumed.
Some challenges are easier.
I mean, maybe I'll check it out soon.
Just to dip my toes into it, you know?
Get a feel for the temperature.
Well, now you say that stuff, Ash.
I'm definitely gonna do it.
I'm gonna do the XXXXL challenge first.
Oh yeah, there's also the greed mode.
I wanna check that out.
Professor Potato, about the specialist dance mod.
Someone mentioned that last time.
I don't think it's a good idea, because I would rather just not know anything about the items.
The fact that your character is gonna dance when he finds a good item, kind of spoils the fact that it's a good item.
You know, I wanna find that out on my own.
I wanna get an item, have something crazy happen and go, Whoa, that's cool!
This item rocks, right?
I wanna get that feeling in my tummy.
You're already greedy?
You're right, I am.
I'm a greedy man.
How many item references are you getting so far?
I mean, not that many.
I've gotten some of the Zelda ones.
Other than that, I don't really notice any references.
What about vine boom mod for explosions?
That sounds hilarious!
Actually, that sounds hilarious, but maybe for like half an hour and then it gets annoying.
Okay, so maybe a mod that does the vine boom, followed by a quick flash of...
What is that guy's name that was popular on Vine once ago?
Like a long...
The guy who's now doing crypto scams and shit.
You know who I mean?
No, it's not him.
It's like someone who was also boxing or something.
A blonde haired dude.
I forget his name.
He's very...
Logan Paul, yes!
That one!
Yeah, yeah.
Just flash his face on the screen with the vine boom for like half a second.
Yeah, the guy who used to do vines once, but then he did like a crypto scam.
That's all I know.
Is he running for president?
Wait, what?
No way.
That's crazy.
Oh my god.
This reminds me of Dark Souls.
There used to be a mod, or maybe there still is in Dark Souls 1, where whenever you died, it would say, thanks, Obama.
Instead of you died.
And for some reason, that just cracked me up.
That is so funny.
It was like a meme at the time, okay?
Maybe I'm a bit old.
But that was a meme, okay?
I also love the...
I don't know if this was a mod once in Dark Souls.
I think it was.
But when you died, it would make the sound effect in Grand Theft Auto.
You know, the camera sound where everything goes red and it slows down.
I think it's from Grand Theft Auto.
There's a mod that when you die, it drops all your items like in Minecraft.
That sounds horrible!
But I mean, if you're dying, you drop the items anyway, right?
Is thanks, Obama, considered old now?
Is it?
I don't know.
Maybe it's not.
It just feels like it was forever ago.
It's just cosmetic, okay.
I mean, those mods are kind of funny.
It's like the mod that someone made for me in Minecraft, where I push a button and the button says, Jim, you know?
Like, that's kind of funny.
It never got old for me.
I love that.
That is such a stupid mod, but it works, you know?
It's effective.
I know, Palicado.
Mugenics has been suggested a lot.
But I feel like that's a game for the far future.
Right now, I'm doing this one.
It's probably gonna take a while because right now, I'm having too much fun with it.
And then I probably don't want to do another roguelike right after, you know?
Maybe we could make the Jim button for Isaac.
Oh, whatever.
You press one of the buttons.
That would be funny.
If you make that, I would use it.
We would have to do it.
That sounds perfect.
You could do it?
That would be amazing.
I mean, honestly, I could probably do it nowadays.
All I do is I pull up Claude in my IDE.
Just say, hey, implement the Jim button.
All right, sir, we'll do.
And then it comes back in two minutes and it's done.
It's crazy what we can do today with the fucking AIs.
It's wild.
Dude, vibe coding is actually a vibe.
It is incredibly addicting.
It is so much fun.
Like maybe a week ago, I spent like seven hours straight.
I could like I didn't even eat for seven hours because I was just so incredibly focused and addicted to doing whatever I was doing in the S code.
Yeah, I'm definitely not coding.
Just letting the AI do it.
I'm pretty much just telling it what to do, right?
Guiding its hand.
It is so much fun.
You know who came up with that term?
Actually, I think it was Andre Carpathi.
One of my favorite dudes of all time.
I love that guy.
If there's anyone you should follow on Twitter or X or whatever it is, you're calling it these days.
Definitely Andre Carpathi.
That guy.
I feel like every tweet it does, I just love reading it, you know?
If I had used the term vibe coding at boot camp, I think the teacher would have slapped me.
Well, of course, the point of that boot camp probably is to teach you how to code, right?
I mean, you don't want to do vibe coding if you don't know how to code to begin with.
Otherwise, you can't really know how to guide the AI and tell it what to do.
I mean, you probably could, but it's not going to be very effective.
You kind of want to be able to verify what's happening, right?
Guys, it's time for me to go.
Thank you so much for watching.
This was a banger.
And we're going to have a stream ASAP again, okay?
If you want to know when the next stream is, either check the schedule on Twitch or join the Discord.
There's always a little event at the top.
You can see when the next stream is.
I will put it in in good time, okay?
Thanks for watching.
I will see you next time.
Bye-bye.